Charles Bukowski papers, 1944-1977
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- IV. Other Publications, 1944-1976
  - Other Publications: Renaissance, vol. 1, no. 3. Signed on cover. 1962 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    "the biggest breasts"
    "information upon an empire of coins"
  - Other Publications: Gallows, vol. 2, no. 1. Last page is full-page advertisement for Run with the Hunted. 1962 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Other Publications: The Outsider, vol. 1, no. 3. Contains an entire section devoted to Charles Bukowski as well as comments and blurbs on Bukowski from many sources. Copy signed on title page. Spring 1963 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    "Charles Bukowski: Poet in a Ruined Landscape" by RR Cuscaden
    "Charles Bukowski: Three Poems" by William Corrington
    Letters from Bukowski to Jon and Lou Webb
    Photographs of Charles Bukowski
    "The Tragedy of Leaves" facsimile holograph with drawings
    "The Priest and the Matador" facsimile holograph with drawings
    "Old Man, Dead in a Room" facsimile holograph with drawings
    "the house"
    "events"
    "dinner, rain and transport"
  - Other Publications: The Outsider, vol. 1, no. 3. Copy in mailing envelope with drawing and notation, "Autographed twice, B." Copy signed with drawing on title page of Charles Bukowski section. Signed full page photo of Bukowski. 1963 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Other Publications: The Outsider, vol. 1, no. 3. Copy in mailing envelope with drawing and notation, "Autographed in Front & by pict. of Buk at typer." Copy signed as presentation to Jon Webb on title page of section and across full page photo "Charles Bukowski 'outsider'-still 1963." 1963 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Other Publications: File on The Outsider, no. 3. 1963 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Advance pull of wrapper, signed
    Page proof of Corrington article
    Page proof with typed signed note by Jon Webb
    Page proofs of the three holograph poems
  - Other Publications: Sciamachy 5. Copy signed on cover. 1963 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    "Existance"
    "Notice"
  - Other Publications: Wormwood Review, vol. 3, no. 4, issue no. 12. Copy signed on cover. 1963 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    "it's not who lived here/but who died here..."
    "Poem for my 43rd Birthday"
    "The End"
  - Other Publications: Sciamachy 6. Copy signed on cover. 1964 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    "Fragile!!"
    "4:30 a.m."
  - Other Publications: The Wormwood Review, vol. 3, no. 4, issue no. 16. Signed at head of title. Selections from Grip the Walls. 1964 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    "the dogs"
    "poetess:
    "The Literary Life"
    "When You Wait for the Dawn..."
    "sleeping woman"
    " the new place"
  - Other Publications: The Wormwood Review, vol. 3, no. 4, issue no. 16. Signed at head of title. Signed inside with drawing. Also signed with presentation inside front cover by editor Marvin Malone. 1964 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Other Publications: Coffin 1 (portfolio). 1964 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    "Waste Paper Basket"
    "The Paper on the Floor"
    "His Wife, the Painter" (this is the original)
    "The Old Man on the Corner"
    Small broadsides, each signed
    Also contains poetry by: Judson Crews, Fielding Dawson, Larry Eigner, EV Griffith, John Barley Hart, Carl Larsen, Mason Jordan Mason, Gil Orlovitz, James Preuss, George Scarbrough, Raymond Souster, Ben Tibbs, George Thompson, James L. Weil.
  - Other Publications: Corrington, John William, Mr. Clean and other poems, San Francisco, Amber House Press. With an introduction by Charles Bukowski. 1964 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Other Publications: Portfolio III, n.p. The Black Sun Press. Presentation copy to John Martin signed on back of Charles Bukowski leaf. 1946 (Box 13)
    "20 tanks from Kasseldown"
    Also contains other works by: Kay Boyle, Sterling Brown, Harry Crosby, David Daiches, James Hanley, Henry Miller, Harry Moore, Selden Rodman, Jean-Paul Sartre, William Abrahams, Hubert Creekmore, Jean Genet, Natalia Ginzberg, Garcia Lorca, Walter Mehring, Waldo Pierce, Kenneth Rexroth, Yvonne Roy, and Stephen Spender.
  - Other Publications: Epos, vol. 16, no. 2. Copy signed on cover. Winter 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Includes: "Advice for Some Young Man in the Year 2046 A.D."
  - Other Publications: Epos, vol. 16, no. 3. Copy signed on cover. Spring 1965 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Includes: "The Terror of the Breath upon the Hand"
  - Other Publications: Epos, vol. 16, no. 4. Signed on the poem. Summer 1965 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Includes: "4:30 a.m."
  - Other Publications: Ante, vol. 1, no. 4. Fall 1965 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    " A Division"
    "Ivan the Terrible"
  - Other Publications: Evidence, issue no. 9. Copy signed on cover. 1965? (Box 14, Folder 5)
    "A Night of Mozart"
    "I Thought of Ships, of Armies, Hangin On..."
    "A Trainride in Hell"
    Also a review of Irving Layton's The Laughing Rooster
    ""The Corybant of Wit"
  - Other Publications: Layton, Irving, The Laughing Rooster, Toronto/Montreal, McClelland and Stewart, Limited. 1964 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Other Publications: Sherman, Jory, My Face in Wax, Chicago, Windfall Press. Signed with an introduction by Charles Bukowski. 1965 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Other Publications: The Wormwood Review, vol. 6, no. 4, issue no. 24. Signed at head of title. Review of Nights Work with drawings by Charles Bukowski. 1966 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    "Buffalo Bill"
    "a little atomic bomb"
    "the colored birds"
    "The Screw-Game"
    "A Beginners Bibliography of Bukowski" by Marvin Malone
  - Other Publications: Richmond, Steven, Hitler Painted Roses, Santa Monica, California, Earth Books and Gallery (Earth Poet Series 1). Foreward by Charles Bukowski. 1966 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Other Publications: Kauri 17. December-November 1966 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Includes: "Moyamensing Prison"
  - Other Publications: Kauri 18. January-February 1967 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Includes: "sometimes when I fell blue I listen to Mahler"
  - Other Publications: Kauri 19. March-April 1967 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Includes: "Notes from Underground"
  - Other Publications: A Tribute to Jim Lowell, Cleveland, Ghost Press. Commentary by Charles Bukowski. 1967 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Other Publications: In New York, vol. 1, issue no. 17. Copy signed on cover. 1967 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Includes "The Ants" and an interview with Charles Bukowski
  - Other Publications: The Outsider, vol. 2, no.4/5. Winter 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    "Kaakaa & other immolations"
    A pressed flower with an explanatory note
    A photocopy of an article of the flooding of the Webb's Tucson printing house
  - Other Publications: Laugh Literary and Man the Humping Guns, vol. 1, no. 1. Edited by Charles Bukowski and Neeli Cherry. Contributing editor, Harold Norse. Copy signed on cover. 1969 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Other Publications: Laugh Literary and Man the Humping Guns, vol. 1, no. 1. Edited by Charles Bukowski and Neeli Cherry. Contributing editor, Harold Norse. Presentation copy to Jim Roman with drawing. 1969 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Other Publications: Laugh Literary and Man the Humping Guns, vol. 1, no. 1. Edited by Charles Bukowski and Neeli Cherry. Contributing editor, Harold Norse. Copy no. 7. Signed by Charles Burkowski and Neeli Cherry, Steve Richmond, and Harold Norse. 1969 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Other Publications: Laugh Literary and Man the Humping Guns, vol. 1, no. 2. Edited by Charles Bukowski and Neeli Cherry. Contributing editor, Harold Norse. Copy signed on cover. Contains extracts from letters to Neeli Cherry. 1969 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Other Publications: Penguin Modern Poets 13: Charles Bukowski, Philip Lamantia, Harold Norse, Harmondsworth, England/Baltimore, Penquin Books, Ltd. A selection of 25 poems. Presentation to Jim Roman with drawing. 1969 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Other Publications: Fox, Hugh, Charles Bukowski: A Critical and Bibliographical Study, Los Angeles, Abyss Publications. Copy signed on cover. 1969 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Other Publications: Dorbin, Sanford, A Bibliography of Charles Bukowski, Los Angeles, Black Sparrow Press. Handbound in boards. Signed by Charles Bukowski and author with an original Bukowski colored ink drawing tipped in. 1969 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Other Publications: Cooley, Seamus, A Checklist of the First One Hundred Publications of the Black Sparrow Press, Los Angeles, Black Sparrow Press. Hardcover. Signed by author and by Robert Kelly ( "Thirty Passing Remarks on the Black Sparrow Press on the Occasion of Its Hundredth Book"). 1971 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Other Publications: A Checklist of the First One Hundred Publications of the Black Sparrow Press, Los Angeles, Black Sparrow Press. Handbound in boards. Signed by the author, Robert Kelly and by 26 Black Sparrow Press authors. 1973 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Other Publications: King, Linda and Charles Bukowski, Me and You Sometimes Love Poems, Los Angeles, Kisskill Press. Signed on cover. 1973 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Other Publications: Small Press Review, vo. 4, no. 4. Copy signed on cover. 1973 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Issue devoted to Charles Bukowski. Contains photos, excerpts from prose and poems, poems, criticism, commentatary on Bukowski by various writers and prose piece by Bukowski "Upon the Mathematics of the Breath and the Way"
  - Other Publications: Second Coming, vol. 2, no. 3. Copy signed on cover. Special issue devoted to Charles Bukowski. 1973 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    "Six Inches"
    "Love Poem to Marina"
    "Poem to a Man in Jail"
    "Layover"
    "The Knifer"
    "Beerbottle"
    Don't Come around but if You Do..."
    "He Beats His Women"
    Also exerpts from poems, stories, letters, criticism and comments on Charles Bukowski by other writers.
  - Other Publications: Six Poets, Ellensburg, Washinton, Vagabond Press. 1973 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    The poets are Al Masarik, Lyn Lifshin, John Thomas, Ronald Koertge, Joel Duetsch, and Ann Menebroker. Charles Bukowski has sketched a portait of each.
  - Other Publications: London Magazine, vol. 13, no. 6. Signed at head of story, "Would You Suggest Writing as a Career?" February-March 1974 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Other Publications: Wormwood, vol. 14, no. 1, issue no. 53. Selections from 55 Beds in the Same Direction". Signed on page 1 and signed by editor Marvin Malone. 1974 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    "200 years"
    "finish"
    "55 beds in the direction"
    "well, now that Ezra has died..."
    "tarot"
    "eleven"
    "no bra, no panties"
    "a bit of light for the toad"
    "demise"
  - Other Publications: Wormwood, vol. 14, no. 1, issue no. 53. Selections from 55 Beds in the Same Direction". Signed on page 1 and signed by editor Marvin Malone. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Other Publications: Poetry Now, vol. 1, no. 6. Copy signed on cover. 1974 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    "2 Horsecollars"
    "The First Love"
    "Your Own Toilet"
    "The Strangest Sight You Ever Did See"
    "Charles Bukowski"
    "William Childress:
    Photos
- V. Audio and Visual Materials, 1960-1980
  - Audio and Visual Materials: TV Guide, v. 23, no. 1176. Notice of half-hour program "Bukowski Reads Bukowski" on Channel 8, Tempe. October 11, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Arcade, the Comic Revue, vol. 1, no. 2. Signed on cover "Bop Bop Against That Curtain." Fall 1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Cover, A New Year's Greeting from the Black Sparrow Press, 1976, Santa Barbara, Black Sparrow Press. Wakoski, Diane, "The Last Poem" and Bukowski, Charles "Tough Company." Wrapper copy in original mailing envelope. 1976 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Cover, A New Year's Greeting from the Black Sparrow Press, 1976, Santa Barbara, Black Sparrow Press. Wakoski, Diane, "The Last Poem" and Bukowski, Charles "Tough Company." Handbound in boards. Signed by both authors. 1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Rolling Stone, issue no. 215. June 17, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    "on photographs"
    "fuzz"
    "dogfight"
    "some people"
    "side of the sun"
    "k.o."
    "palm leaves"
    "BUK: the Pock-marked Poetry of Charles Bukowski"
    Glenn Easterly with photos by Tony Lane and excerpts from poetry and prose
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Chilled Green, Detroit, Alternative Press. Signed postcard. (Volume 17, Folder 1)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: His Wife, The Painter, Hearse Broadside, 1. Signed facsimile. 1960 (Volume 17, Folder 2)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Face of a Political Candidate on a Street Billboard, Ann Arbor, The Old Marble Press. Signed broadside. 1975 (Volume 17, Folder 3)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Love Poem to Marina, Los Angeles, Black Sparrow Press. Broadside. Two copies, one signed and one unsigned. 1973 (Volume 17, Folder 4)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: to kiss the worms goodnight, Los Angeles, Black Sparrow Press. Signed broadside. 1966 (Volume 17, Folder 5)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: On Going Out to Get the Mail, Los Angeles, Black Sparrow Press. Signed broadside. 1966 (Volume 17, Folder 6)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: the girls/For the Mercy-Mongers, Los Angeles, Black Sparrow Press. Signed broadside. 1966 (Volume 17, Folder 7)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: The Flower Lover/I Met a Genius, Los Angeles, Black Sparrow Press. Signed broadside. 1966 (Volume 17, Folder 8)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Mockingbird Wish Me Luck, Los Angeles, Black Sparrow Press. Three copies all signed. 1972 (Volume 17, Folder 9)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: 86'd, Pasco, Washington, Goldermood Rainbow Press. Four signed broadsides. (Volume 17, Folder 10)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Winter, Evanston, No Mountain Poetry Project. Boradside number 4 signed. 1975 (Volume 17, Folder 11)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Bukowski, a film by Trevor Hackford and Richard Davies. Poster. (Related material found in Box2 Folder 10). (Volume 17, Folder 12)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Charles Bukowski im Maro-Verlag. Poster. (Volume 17, Folder 13)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Poetry--Charles Bukowski, Steven Richmond. Recording signed by both poets. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Bukowski, 90 Minutes in Hell, Santa Monica, Earth Books. (Recording made in 1966.) 1977 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Bukowski poems & insults!, San Francisco, Bitter Lemon Records. Recorded live 1973. Four copies all signed. 1975 (Box 18, Folder 3-6)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Bukowski reads his poetry, Los Angeles, Takoma Records. Signed. Four audio cassettes. 1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Nola Express. Three copies. 1970 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Six Acrylics all signed "Buk." (Volume 19, Folder 1)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Three Items. 1965, 1967 (Volume 19, Folder 2)
    A Ink self portrait, "Buk'65 /New Orleans"
    Pencil, self portrait, "Buk /'67"
    Ink, patients and nurse, "Buk"
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Signed watercolor "Buk." (A new penny since lost, was attached at upper right.) (Volume 19, Folder 3)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Three Watercolors Signed "Buk". 1964 (Volume 19, Folder 4)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Watercolor Signed "Buk." 1963 (Volume 19, Folder 5)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Ink Self-portrait, "Buk 65." 1965 (Volume 19, Folder 6)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: In Self-Portrait, "Buk '65/N.O. La./March/Minne's /Place." 1965 (Volume 19, Folder 7)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: A-J "wax chalks." (A has another drawing on the back.) All signed "Buk 66." 1966 (Volume 19, Folder 8)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Acrylic, "Buk." (Volume 19, Folder 9)
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Two Items. 1964 (Volume 19, Folder 10)
    A Watercolor, "Buk 1964/God is Sad"
    B Watercolor, "Buk k6"
  - Audio and Visual Materials: Collage of Five Ink Drawings and Pencil. Each drawing signed "Buk '64." One is titled "A Hotel for Stragglers." 1964 (Volume 19, Folder 11)